Can your existing vehicle get to 100 million?
Yes.
Will it probably take 15 years?
Are you okay with that?
That feels long.
I think in my brain, I'm doing other things in 10 years.
You might not see yourself in 10 years doing it
because you think about this times 10.
If in 10 years you were doing 40 million a year,
your life's different.
Your life at the pinnacle of success
in every business is the same.
Whether you sell widgets, back massages, or motorcycles,
it's gonna be the same thing.
Everyone feels like their business is really unique,
but the higher up you go, it's the same shit.
Maybe the biggest gift that I can give you
is that there is nothing on the other side of this rainbow.